{
   "Role Functional":[
      {
         "1. Analyze product structures - KC1":[
            {
               "question":"When can you create precise assemblies in Active Workspace?",
               "options":[
                  "If we apply the Latest Working revision rule",
                  "If we apply the Precise Only revision rule",
                  "Editing values in the Precise column",
                  "Precise assemblies can be viewed, but not created in Active Worskpace"
               ],
               "correct":"Editing values in the Precise column",
               "type":"radio"
            },
            {
               "question":"For a component that has only revision A, approved, and revision B, working, the Latest Working revision rule would select which of the following?",
               "options":[
                  "Revision A",
                  "Revision B",
                  "Neither"
               ],
               "correct":"Revision B",
               "type":"radio"
            },
            {
               "question":"When we open an assembly, what happens?",
               "options":[
                  "The global revision rule will be applied if we open it for the first time",
                  "The assembly will not load any revisions and wait for us to manually select a revision rule",
                  "The assembly will always be loaded using the Latest Working revision rule, but we can change that later on",
                  "The assembly will always be loaded using the Any Status; Working revision rule, but we can change that later on"
               ],
               "correct":"The global revision rule will be applied if we open it for the first time",
               "type":"radio"
            },
            {
               "question":"A working context contains what?",
               "options":[
                  "Just one assembly",
                  "Just one assembly and one revision rule",
                  "One or several configured assemblies",
                  "One or several unconfigured assemblies"
               ],
               "correct":"One or several configured assemblies",
               "type":"radio"
            },
            {
               "question":"Imprecise structures need to be configured using a revision rule.",
               "options":[
                  "TRUE",
                  "FALSE"
               ],
               "correct":"TRUE",
               "type":"radio"
            },
            {
               "question":"Working contexts are always visible to everyone.",
               "options":[
                  "TRUE",
                  "FALSE"
               ],
               "correct":"FALSE",
               "type":"radio"
            },
            {
               "question":"We can compare two revisions of the same item.",
               "options":[
                  "TRUE",
                  "FALSE"
               ],
               "correct":"FALSE",
               "type":"radio"
            },
            {
               "question":"We can choose to compare only the leaf nodes of our assembly.",
               "options":[
                  "TRUE",
                  "FALSE"
               ],
               "correct":"TRUE",
               "type":"radio"
            }
         ]
      }
   ],
   "Role Admin":[
      {
         "1 Install the Business Modeler IDE (BMIDE)":[
            {
               "question":"In BMIDE, what is IDE an abbreviation for?",
               "options":[
                  "Interface Desktop Environment",
                  "Interface Design Elements",
                  "Integrated Drive Electronics",
                  "Integrated Development Environment"
               ],
               "correct":"Integrated Development Environment",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"The _tcbaseline.XML file ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "contains a snapshot of the template data model",
                  "lists the template XML files included in the data model",
                  "contains the data model for this template",
                  "lists the other templates that this template is built on top of"
               ],
               "correct":"contains a snapshot of the template data model",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"The _dependancy.XML file ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "contains a snapshot of the template data model",
                  "lists the template XML files included in the data model",
                  "contains the data model for this template",
                  "lists the other templates that this template is built on top of"
               ],
               "correct":"lists the other templates that this template is built on top of",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"The _template.XML file ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "contains a snapshot of the template data model",
                  "lists the template XML files included in the data model",
                  "contains the data model for this template",
                  "lists the other templates that this template is built on top of"
               ],
               "correct":"contains the data model for this template",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"The master.XML file ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "contains a snapshot of the template data model",
                  "lists the template XML files included in the data model",
                  "contains the data model for this template",
                  "lists the other templates that this template is built on top of"
               ],
               "correct":"lists the template XML files included in the data model",
               "type":"checkbox"
            }
         ],
         "1. Install Teamcenter databases":[
            {
               "question":"What is the minimum RAM required to run BMIDE with live updates?",
               "options":[
                  ".5 GB",
                  "1 GB",
                  "2 GB",
                  "5 GB"
               ],
               "correct":"2 GB",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"On which tier is persistent metadata stored?",
               "options":[
                  "Resource tier",
                  "Enterprise tier",
                  "Web tier",
                  "Routing tier"
               ],
               "correct":"Resource tier",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"When installing Teamcenter, when should the database be installed?",
               "options":[
                  "First",
                  "Second",
                  "Third",
                  "Fourth"
               ],
               "correct":"First",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Which of these statements is not true regarding Teamcenter database support?",
               "options":[
                  "Oracle is supported",
                  "Microsoft SQL Server is supported",
                  "Microsoft Access is supported",
                  "All of the above are supported"
               ],
               "correct":"Microsoft Access is supported",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"When installing Oracle, it is recommeded that you use ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "Teamcenter Oracle database templates",
                  "Teamcenter generic database templates",
                  "Oracle database templates",
                  "Microsoft database templates"
               ],
               "correct":"Teamcenter Oracle database templates",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What Oracle account is created to hold your Teamcenter data?",
               "options":[
                  "sys",
                  "infodba",
                  "tc",
                  "system"
               ],
               "correct":"infodba",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Which is NOT a major component of an Oracle installation?",
               "options":[
                  "Server",
                  "Database",
                  "Volume",
                  "Listener"
               ],
               "correct":"Volume",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What is included in an Oracle instance?",
               "options":[
                  "Only the System Global Area",
                  "Only Oracle processes",
                  "The Oracle Server",
                  "The combination of the System Global Area and Oracle processes"
               ],
               "correct":"The combination of the System Global Area and Oracle processes",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"When choosing an Oracle install location, which statement is false?",
               "options":[
                  "You can install the Oracle server and application files on shared directories",
                  "Oracle does not support database files on shared directories",
                  "To improve performance, create database files on remote disk drives",
                  "To ensure data integrity, create database files on local disk drives"
               ],
               "correct":"To improve performance, create database files on remote disk drives",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What is the purpose of the Oracle listener?",
               "options":[
                  "Monitors connection requests from one database or for multiple databases",
                  "Monitors email requests to the database",
                  "Monitors file requests from the local server",
                  "Monitors SQL queries from a 4tier client"
               ],
               "correct":"Monitors SQL queries from a 4tier client",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What file does a Teamcenter client use to connect to the database?",
               "options":[
                  "listener.ora",
                  "tnsnames.ora",
                  "portal.bat",
                  "tcdata.bat"
               ],
               "correct":"tnsnames.ora",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What Oracle database service must be running in order for Teamcenter to connect to the database?",
               "options":[
                  "System Global Area",
                  "Server",
                  "Client",
                  "Listener"
               ],
               "correct":"Listener",
               "type":"checkbox"
            }
         ],
         "1. Install the corporate server":[
            {
               "question":"When using the Microsoft SQL database, which of the following is False?",
               "options":[
                  "The Teamcenter corporate server can be installed on Windows or UNIX platforms",
                  "The Teamcenter corporate server must be installed on a Windows platform",
                  "Twotier clients must be installed on Windows platform",
                  "Fourtier clients can be installed on Windows or UNIX platforms"
               ],
               "correct":"The Teamcenter corporate server can be installed on Windows or UNIX platforms",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"In Teamcenter, FMS is an abbreviation for ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "Fully Managed Service",
                  "Flexible Modeling System",
                  "File Management System",
                  "Firewall Modulation Subsystem"
               ],
               "correct":"File Management System",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Which statement is true regarding a Teamcenter 4-tier architecture install?",
               "options":[
                  "The FSC is found on the client tier",
                  "The FSC is found on the corporate tier",
                  "The FSC is found on the web tier",
                  "The FSC is found on the resource tier"
               ],
               "correct":"The FSC is found on the corporate tier",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Which of the following does the Teamcenter corporate server NOT contain?",
               "options":[
                  "A database",
                  "Shared binary executables and files",
                  "Shared data subdirectories and files",
                  "Volumes"
               ],
               "correct":"A database",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Which is NOT an important component of the corporate server?",
               "options":[
                  "TC_ROOT",
                  "TC_DATA",
                  "TC_LICENSE",
                  "FMS"
               ],
               "correct":"TC_LICENSE",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What provides file transfer between volumes and clients?",
               "options":[
                  "WAN",
                  "FCC",
                  "FSC",
                  "FMS"
               ],
               "correct":"FMS",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Which process controls the transfer of data between volumes and clients?",
               "options":[
                  "WAN",
                  "FCC",
                  "FSC",
                  "FMS"
               ],
               "correct":"FSC",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"When selecting Teamcenter features to install, you should install ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "only the solutions and features you need",
                  "all the solutions and features available",
                  "only one additional feature",
                  "the same list of features that some one else you know installed"
               ],
               "correct":"only the solutions and features you need",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"A Teamcenter configuration is ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "a set of one or more solutions to be installed",
                  "a set of one or more features to be installed",
                  "a set of one or more solutions or features to be installed",
                  "a set of one or more solutions and features to be installed"
               ],
               "correct":"a set of one or more solutions and features to be installed",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Each TC_ROOT is ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "a set of TC_DATA directories",
                  "a single Teamcenter installation",
                  "a separate configuration",
                  "a set of multiple configurations"
               ],
               "correct":"a separate configuration",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What is the purpose of the Dispatcher Server feature?",
               "options":[
                  "Installs the file management system",
                  "Installs the process that manages the pool of Teamcenter server processes",
                  "Installs Teamcenter 2tier or 4tier Rich Clients",
                  "Installs the scheduler module and event client for file translation"
               ],
               "correct":"Installs the scheduler module and event client for file translation",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Which file is used to set most of the environment variables that are needed to run Teamcenter?",
               "options":[
                  "tc_env.bat",
                  "tc_profilesvars.bat",
                  "tnsnames.ora",
                  "tcdata.bat"
               ],
               "correct":"tc_profilesvars.bat",
               "type":"checkbox"
            }
         ]
      }
   ],
   "Role Parameter":[
      {
         "1. Administer lists of values (LOVs)":[
            {
               "question":"___ is not a classic LOV.",
               "options":[
                  "Filter LOVs",
                  "Cascading LOVs (Hierarchical)",
                  "Interdependent cascading LOVs",
                  "Dynamic LOVs"
               ],
               "correct":"Dynamic LOVs",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"____ are lists of values that are a subset of another LOV.",
               "options":[
                  "Filter LOVs",
                  "Cascading LOVs (Hierarchical)",
                  "Interdependent cascading LOVs",
                  "Dynamic LOVs"
               ],
               "correct":"Filter LOVs",
               "type":"checkbox"
            }
         ],
         "1. Identify Business Modeler IDE (BMIDE) fundamentals - 14.1":[
            {
               "question":"____ are lists of values queried from the database when the user selects the dropdown list.",
               "options":[
                  "Filter LOVs",
                  "Cascading LOVs (Hierarchical)",
                  "Interdependent cascading LOVs",
                  "Dynamic LOVs"
               ],
               "correct":"Dynamic LOVs",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"For a template project prefix, what numeric digits can be used?",
               "options":[
                  "19",
                  "39",
                  "49",
                  "03"
               ],
               "correct":"49",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"How can you modify a COTS element?",
               "options":[
                  "A COTS element cannot be modified in the foundation template",
                  "A COTS element cannot be modified in the project template",
                  "A modified COTS element is added to a dependent template",
                  "The COTS element is removed from the template"
               ],
               "correct":"A COTS element cannot be modified in the foundation template",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What is the best practice to manage custom BMIDE templates?",
               "options":[
                  "Managed in a PLM system",
                  "Managed on a shared drive",
                  "Managed in a SCM system",
                  "Managed in a folder"
               ],
               "correct":"Managed in a SCM system",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"Once you setup Project Backup settings, what appears upon deploying the project?",
               "options":[
                  "The project deploys to the server",
                  "A dialog box will prompt to backup the template",
                  "A dialog box will prompt to save the template",
                  "Confirmation of the deploy"
               ],
               "correct":"A dialog box will prompt to backup the template",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"How can you manipulate the visibility of business objects in the “configure business objects to display” window?",
               "options":[
                  "Remove the business objects from the filter",
                  "Remove the COTS objects",
                  "Hide the business objects",
                  "Turn the business objects off"
               ],
               "correct":"Remove the business objects from the filter",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What do constants control?",
               "options":[
                  "List of property options",
                  "Govern global system behavior",
                  "Govern the behaviors of business objects",
                  "Deploy data model updates to the client"
               ],
               "correct":"Govern global system behavior",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"What do rules control?",
               "options":[
                  "List of property options",
                  "Govern global system behavior",
                  "Govern the behaviors of business objects",
                  "Deploy data model updates to the client"
               ],
               "correct":"Govern the behaviors of business objects",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"When do you use a Hot Deploy method?",
               "options":[
                  "Development environment",
                  "Development and QA environments",
                  "Development, QA, and Production environments",
                  "QA and Production environments"
               ],
               "correct":"Development environment",
               "type":"checkbox"
            },
            {
               "question":"A server connection profile is used to ____ .",
               "options":[
                  "deploy extensions to a server",
                  "establish a connection to the Teamcenter server",
                  "save the deploy.log file to the server",
                  "install the Business Modeler IDE"
               ],
               "correct":"establish a connection to the Teamcenter server",
               "type":"checkbox"
            }
         ]
      }
   ]
}